[Plot Love II]
[مؤامرة الحب الثاني]
[Episode 21]
[الحلقة 21]
Su Manni.
حول ماني.
Why do you seduce all men?
لماذا تغري كل الرجال؟
Who am I seducing?
من أنا أغوي؟
You tell me.
أخبرني أنت.
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
Who did you seduce last time
من الذي قمت بإغوائه في المرة السابقة
at the Royal Court Hotel?
في فندق رويال كورت؟
Don't you remember?
الا تتذكر؟
Don't talk nonsense.
لا تتحدث عن هراء.
Su Manni.
حول ماني.
I don't care if you seduce other men.
لا يهمني إذا كنت تغري الرجال الآخرين.
But Lu Nan is your brother-in-law.
لكن لو نان هو صهرك.
Don't you find it disgusting
لا تجده مقرف
to seduce your brother-in-law?
لإغواء صهرك؟
You!
أنت!
I am not Su Bei.
أنا لست Su Bei.
I'm not as kind as her.
أنا لست لطيفًا مثلها.
Also,
ايضا،
listen.
استمع.
If you dare to bully Su Bei
إذا كنت تجرؤ على التنمر على Su Bei
or seduce Lu Nan again,
أو إغواء لو نان مرة أخرى ،
I will not let you go.
لن اسمح لك باذهاب.
[Fitting room]
[غرفة ملائمة]
Did you do it?
هل فعلتها؟
What did you say?
ماذا قلت؟
Did you expose my stuff?
هل فضحت أشيائي؟
What's in it for me to do this?
ما الفائدة من القيام بذلك؟
You're jealous that
أنت غيور ذلك
I got Aisha's endorsement.
حصلت على تأييد عائشة.
Don't you forget what happened
لا تنسى ما حدث
in the preliminary round?
في الجولة التمهيدية؟
I have your number.
لدي رقم هاتفك.
Enough.
كافية.
Think about it.
فكر في الأمر.
Since you have my number,
بما أن رقم هاتفي ،
how could I do this?
كيف أستطيع فعل هذا؟
So who will it be?
وعليه من ستكون؟
Think about it carefully.
فكر في الأمر بعناية.
You didn't even
أنت لم تفعل ذلك حتى
go to the last game.
اذهب إلى المباراة الأخيرة.
Ye Ting said to investigate you thoroughly.
قال يي تينغ للتحقيق معك بدقة.
Do you think others
هل تفكر بالآخرين
can't find what I found?
لا أجد ما وجدته؟
You mean Su Bei wants to get revenge on me?
تقصد أن Su Bei تريد الانتقام مني؟
I am going for her.
انا ذاهب لها
Hold on.
يتمسك.
If you just went to her like that,
إذا ذهبت إليها للتو بهذه الطريقة ،
would she tell you?
هل ستخبرك
I can't just let it go.
لا يمكنني ترك الأمر يذهب.
All right.
حسنا.
Calm down.
هدء من روعك.
Think carefully.
فكر جيدًا.
Su Bei is the wife of Huanzhen's president.
Su Bei هي زوجة رئيس Huanzhen.
Could you afford to offend her?
هل يمكنك تحمل الإساءة لها؟
Don't worry.
لا تقلق.
I'll dig it out
سأحفرها
for you.
لك.
Have you heard of it?
هل سمعت بها؟
Someone just saw Su Bei and Mr. Lu
شخص ما رأى سو باي والسيد لو
break up downstairs.
تفكك الطابق السفلي.
They broke up?
انفصلوا؟
They were so sweet
كانوا حلوين جدا
and I was so envious.
وكنت حسودًا جدًا.
Su Bei.
مع باي.
Now that you've given up your position,
الآن بعد أن تخلت عن منصبك ،
I can't live up to your kindness.
لا أستطيع أن أرقى إلى مستوى لطفك.
Nan has always been
لطالما كان نان
absent-minded during this time.
شارد الذهن خلال هذا الوقت.
How could he put such an important contract
كيف يمكنه وضع مثل هذا العقد المهم
in the bathroom?
في الحمام؟
Maybe brother has been very busy at work recently.
ربما كان أخي مشغولاً للغاية في العمل مؤخرًا.
What if the nanny didn't see it
ماذا لو لم تراها المربية
and the contract would be damaged?
وسوف يتضرر العقد؟
Grandma, don't worry.
جدتي ، لا تقلقي.
I will send it to brother tomorrow.
سأرسله إلى الأخ غدا.
Okay.
تمام.
Brother.
أخ.
Nan.
في.
Nan, what's up?
نان ، ما الأمر؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Nan.
في.
Brother, you drank?
أخي هل شربت؟
Feier.
احتفال.
Let the nanny make the hangover soup.
دع المربية تصنع حساء المخلفات.
Okay.
تمام.
Nan.
في.
Grandma.
الجدة.
If you have something to say,
إذا كان لديك ما تقوله ،
don't hold it in your heart,
لا تحبسها في قلبك
just tell me.
فقط أخبرني.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Go to rest.
اذهب للراحة.
Leave me alone.
اتركني وحدي.
Nan.
في.
What happened to you?
ما حدث لك؟
I broke up with Bei.
لقد انفصلت عن باي.
I thought
اعتقدت
Huanzhen was the most important thing
كان Huanzhen أهم شيء
to me.
إلي
But why does
لكن لماذا
losing Bei
يخسر باي
hurt me so much?
يؤلمني كثيرا؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
Tell me.
أخبرني.
Is it rare
هل هو نادر
to meet someone
لمقابلة شخص ما
with whom you truly love each other?
مع من تحب بعضكما البعض حقا؟
I met Su Bei.
قابلت Su Bei.
But now
لكن الآن
I lost her.
لقد فقدتها.
Nan.
في.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Your parents left early.
غادر والداك مبكرا.
I watch you grow up little by little.
أشاهدك تكبر شيئًا فشيئًا.
I'm so glad
أنا جد مسرور
you're finally
انت اخيرا
in charge of our group.
المسؤول عن مجموعتنا.
Grandma.
الجدة.
I am getting old.
أنا أتقدم في السن.
I look forward to
أنا أتطلع إلى
seeing you
رؤيتكم
get married
تزوج
and have children
ولديهم أطفال
in my lifetime.
في حياتي.
So I kept
لذلك ظللت
urging you so much
يحثك كثيرا
that I forgot
التي نسيتها
how you felt.
كيف شعرت.
Nan.
في.
Grandma, don't cry.
جدتي لا تبكي.
Maybe
يمكن
it's really my fault.
إنه خطأي حقًا.
Grandma.
الجدة.
Feier.
احتفال.
Take good care of your brother.
اعتني بأخيك جيدًا.
Okay.
تمام.
Brother.
أخ.
You are drunk.
انت ثمل.
Take some hangover soup.
خذ بعض حساء المخلفات.
Bei.
في.
Brother.
أخ.
Don't be sad.
لا تحزن.
I will always be with you.
سأبقى دائما معك.
You still have me.
لازلت معك.
Why?
لماذا ا؟
Why did she leave me?
لماذا تركتني؟
Are you leaving?
هل أنت ذاهب؟
Bei.
في.
Actually,
في الحقيقة،
I'm not insisting that you break up.
أنا لا أصر على الانفصال.
I will not interfere in your affairs
لن أتدخل في شؤونك
from now on.
من الان فصاعدا.
Grandma.
الجدة.
I didn't break up with Lu Nan
أنا لم أنفصل عن لو نان
because of you.
بسببك.
There are too many problems between the two of us.
هناك الكثير من المشاكل بيننا.
Take your time
خذ وقتك
to fix the problems.
لإصلاح المشاكل.
Bei.
في.
Come home with me
تأتي معي إلى البيت
to see Nan, will you?
لترى نان ، أليس كذلك؟
Grandma.
الجدة.
I haven't figured out
أنا لم أحسب
what's going on between us.
ما الذي يحدث بيننا.
Please give me some time.
من فضلك أعطني بعض الوقت.
Bei.
في.
Where are you going without having breakfast?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب دون تناول الإفطار؟
I have no appetite. You enjoy yourselves.
ليس لدي أي شهية.  تستمتعون بأنفسكم.
How can you have the strength
كيف يمكنك الحصول على القوة
to chase my granddaughter-in-law back if you don't eat?
لمطاردة حفيدة زوجي إذا لم تأكل؟
Grandma?
الجدة؟
Who is the granddaughter-in-law you speak of?
من هي حفيدة الابن التي تتحدث عنها؟
Who else
من أيضا
besides Su Bei?
بجانب Su Bei؟
I won't interfere
لن أتدخل
in your affairs with Su Bei any more.
في شؤونك مع Su Bei بعد الآن.
I am getting old.
أنا أتقدم في السن.
Your life is up to yourselves.
حياتك متروكة لأنفسكم.
Thank you, grandma!
شكرا لك جدتي!
Look at you.
انظر لحالك.
Have breakfast now.
تناول الفطور الآن.
Let's eat together.
دعونا نأكل معا.
Come on.
هيا.
Ye Ting. Your alarm clock.
أيها تينغ.  المنبه الخاص بك.
Su Bei.
مع باي.
Why don't we take a leave of absence
لماذا لا نأخذ إجازة
from work today?
من العمل اليوم؟
How uncomfortable it is
كم هو غير مريح
for you to meet Lu Nan.
لكي تقابل لو نان.
No way. I still have game design to do.
مستحيل.  لا يزال لدي تصميم لعبة لأقوم به.
What an able woman.
يا لها من امرأة قادرة.
So couples
حتى الأزواج
had better not work in one company.
كان من الأفضل ألا يعمل في شركة واحدة.
It would be embarrassing
سيكون محرجا
if they broke up.
إذا انفصلا.
I'm going to wash up.
سوف اغتسل.
Okay.
تمام.
Why are you here?
لماذا أنت هنا؟
Didn't you say leave me alone?
ألم تقل اتركني وشأني؟
Why are you still angry after so long?
لماذا لا تزال غاضبًا بعد كل هذا الوقت الطويل؟
I brought your favorite tiramisu.
أحضرت التيراميسو المفضل لديك.
I'm not a child anymore.
لم أعد طفلاً.
Do you think a cake is enough to coax me?
هل تعتقد أن كعكة كافية لإقناعي؟
You are always a child in my heart.
أنت دائما طفل في قلبي.
Then why did you hit me?
إذن لماذا ضربتني؟
It's my fault.
هذا خطأي.
I apologize to you.
انا اعتذر لك.
But why didn't you discuss with me
لكن لماذا لم تناقشي معي
before signing with Huanzhen?
قبل التوقيع مع Huanzhen؟
What if I discussed with you?
ماذا لو ناقشت معك؟
You wouldn't agree.
لن توافق.
I don't understand.
لا أفهم.
What's so good about Huanzhen?
ما الجيد في Huanzhen؟
Mr. Ye.
السيد.  هو.
Su Bei.
مع باي.
♪Another♪
♪ آخر ♪
♪Long talk all night♪
♪ حديث طويل طوال الليل ♪
♪I haven't finished drinking the water on the table♪
لم أنتهي من شرب الماء على المائدة
♪I stare at the windowsill♪
أحدق في حافة النافذة
♪That fallen flower is no longer blooming♪
♪ تلك الزهرة الساقطة لم تعد تتفتح
♪You always say♪
♪ أنت دائما تقول ♪
♪Like and love♪
♪ اعجاب وحب ♪
♪Are similar but different♪
♪ متشابهة لكنها مختلفة ♪
♪Finally this time I'm being depended on too♪
♪ أخيرًا هذه المرة أنا أعتمد أيضًا
♪Listen and cover up, learn to sigh♪
♪ استمع وتستر وتعلم التنهد ♪
♪How happy you are laughing♪
♪ ما مدى سعادتك بالضحك
♪You are planning your future with her♪
♪ أنت تخططين لمستقبلك معها
♪I'm so numb, but I'm♪
♪ أنا مخدر جدًا ، لكنني ♪
♪Still listening♪
♪ ما زلت تستمع ♪
♪I don't have to guess your mind anymore♪
♪ ليس عليّ أن أخمن عقلك بعد الآن ♪
♪Is it funny, sad or helpless♪
♪ هل هو مضحك أم حزين أم عاجز ♪
♪Adults shouldn't lose their temper easily♪
♪ لا ينبغي أن يفقد البالغون أعصابهم بسهولة ♪